<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types on BeaconStreet USA</title>
    <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/category/myers-briggs-personality-types/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Myers-Briggs Personality Types on BeaconStreet USA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:10:48 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/category/myers-briggs-personality-types/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Famous People and Their Myers-Briggs Personality Types—Part 1: The Extraverts</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-1-the-extraverts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-1-the-extraverts/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, Myers-Briggs experts have analyzed many famous people to make educated guesses of their personality types. While most celebrities, past and present, have never taken a personality test, psychologists who are knowledgeable about typology believe they know what the outcomes would be.
Most politicians, entertainers, and leaders of large organizations are extraverts. Introverts are usually deep thinkers, complex individuals who can be charming in public but are private in their personal lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ meets ENTJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-entj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-entj/</guid>
      <description>INFJs and ENTJs are on the same wavelength in many ways. They enjoy spending time together and sharing creative, stimulating conversations. Superficial topics bore them. Both have excellent intuition and can size people up accurately on short acquaintance. They share the ability to comprehend complex situations that baffle others.
While the two types can become close friends, INFJs should be mindful of the ENTJ’s rough edges. This type can be blunt, with little tolerance for mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ISTJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-istj-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 02:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-istj-2/</guid>
      <description>It’s fair to say that any two people with this combination of Myers-Briggs traits are likely to have adjustment problems if they’re to function smoothly together. While they are joined in their preference for privacy (introversion), this isn’t enough to make them compatible. Both have a preference for judging, as well, but they use the function in dissimilar ways due to their other trait differences.
The INFJ is introverted (I), intuitive (N), feeling (F), and judging (J).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Distribution by Myers-Briggs Type</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-type-and-career-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-type-and-career-choice/</guid>
      <description>A 14-year study of thousands of Americans in various careers shows that different Myers-Biggs types have different preferences and skills relating to the jobs they take. When the data were analyzed at the end of the 14 years, researchers found that people of various Myers-Briggs categories most often held the following jobs listed below.
Career Distribution by Myers-Briggs Type
ISTJ: Administrators in schools, industry, and health care, dentists, police and detectives,auditors and accountants ISFJ: Nurses, clerical supervisors, preschool teachers, librarians, health technicians INFJ: Education consultants, clergy, physicians, media specialists, teachers (English, art, drama) INTJ: Lawyers, scientists, computer systems analysts, chemical engineers, university teachers ISTP: Farmers, mechanics and repairers, electrical technicians, engineers, dental hygienists ISFP: Storekeepers and stock clerks, nurses, dental assistants, bookkeepers, mechanics and repairers INFP: Psychiatrists and psychologists, writers, artists, and editors, teachers, social workers, musicians and composers INTP: Writers, artists and entertainers, computer programmers, social scientists ESTP: Marketing personnel, police and detectives, managers and administrators, retail salespeople, auditors ESFP: child care workers, receptionists, salespeople, religious workers, teachers (preschool) ENFP: Rehabilitation counselors, teachers (art and drama), writers, artists, entertainers, psychologists, clergy ENTP: Photographers, marketing personnel, salespeople, journalists, computer systems analysts ESTJ: Teachers, school administrators, surgeons, factory and site supervisors, lawyers ESFJ: Medical secretaries, clergy, nurses, home economists, hairdressers and cosmetologists ENFJ: Clergy, teachers, actors and entertainers, writers and artists, consultants ENTJ: Lawyers, managers, mortgage brokers, administrators (computer systems and education), scientists The study data do not indicate which careers are best for certain types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Depression Profiles—INFJ vs. INFP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/depression-profiles-infj-vs-infp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/depression-profiles-infj-vs-infp/</guid>
      <description>The Myers-Briggs types INFJ and INFP are affected by depression more than most other types. Both are Introverted (I), intuitive (N), and feeling (F). This means that they have a compassionate nature, see the underlying meaning of events around them and have trouble shielding themselves from the pain of others, particularly in the face of indifference of others. They puzzle about why they are so powerless to change things. They realize that they were meant for greater things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous People and Their Myers-Briggs Personality Types: Part 2, the Introverts</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-2-the-introverts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-2-the-introverts/</guid>
      <description>The Myers-Briggs personality test has been used to analyze many famous people. While most celebrities, past and present, have never taken a personality test, psychologists who are knowledgeable about typology believe they know what the outcomes would be.
Introverts are usually deep thinkers, complex individuals who can be charming in public but are private in their personal lives. Introverts aren’t easily categorized or put in boxes. Most politicians, entertainers, and leaders of large organizations are extraverts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ESFJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-esfj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-esfj/</guid>
      <description>When an INFJ and ESFJ are drawn to each other, the attraction becomes obvious fairly quickly— although the ESFJ is usually the more transparent of the two and is likely to make the first overtures. INFJs are generally cautious until they’re sure of a relationship.
ESFJs are generous and outgoing, giving without any thought of return. If someone expresses a need, they’re among the first to try to satisfy it. They place a high value on harmony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ESFP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-esfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-esfp/</guid>
      <description>What happens when an INFJ meets an ESFP? Is there an instant attraction? Do they repel each other like two magnets?
Looking at their personality traits, you’d think they have little in common. When an early attraction persists, it’s cause for wonder. Usually, the bond is associated with their shared feeling (F) trait.
Introversion (I) vs. Extraversion (E)
The first big difference lies in the INFJ’s need for privacy vs. the ESFP’s preference for social contact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ESTJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-estj-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-estj-2/</guid>
      <description>All things considered, the attraction between the ESTJs and INFJs isn’t surprising. Because ESTJs are conventional people, they prefer colorful partners to make their lives more interesting. They aren’t drawn to other ESTJs. INFJs have creative minds and supply the friendly, playful traits ESTJs are missing. The INFJ, in turn, is rewarded by an appreciative audience.
An INFJ may find ESTJ friends too direct and outspoken. They tend to overlook polite ways of dealing with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ meets INTP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-intp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-intp/</guid>
      <description>INFJs are often drawn to INTPs because of their intelligence and ability to apply logic to every situation. Eventually, though, INFJs tend to find most INTPs distant because of their unemotional approach to life. The INTP is attracted to INFJs because of their compassion and spontaneity. But the qualities that drew them to an INFJ in the first place can eventually get on their nerves. To them, it’s sloppy to let feelings override logic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ meets ISFJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-isfj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-isfj/</guid>
      <description>INFJs and ISFJs are alike in many ways. They’re introverted, feeling, and judging. They differ only on the intuitive/sensing dimension of the Myers-Briggs Inventory. Both types put much of their energy into helping others and share a drive to make the world a better place. People can count on them in times of trouble.
Although INFJs and ISFJs have high ideals, they’re modest about them. They prefer to make their values apparent in their actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ISFP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-isfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-isfp/</guid>
      <description>As one of sixteen Myers-Briggs types, the INFJ is introverted (I), intuitive (N), feeling (F), and judging (J). A little different from the ISFP—who shares the introverted (I) and feeling (F) traits but not the intuitive (N) and judging (J) traits.
Both have a need for some privacy to collect themselves and regroup. If the INFJ says to an ISFP partner, “I think I’ll go out and straighten up the garage,” the ISFP is likely to interpret this as a need for time alone and say “Good idea,” rather than “Want me to come?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ISTP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-istp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-istp/</guid>
      <description>It’s obvious looking at the letters I-N-F-J and I-S-T-P that these two Myers-Briggs personality types are very different. The only trait they have in common is their introversion. Both types enjoy privacy. They find meaning not from superficial experiences but from their contemplation of them.
Sensing vs. Intuition
Because ISTPs rely on their sensing preference more than their intuition, they are driven to understand how things work. They usually have good eye-hand coordination, which makes them skilled at fixing things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Men as Lovers</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-men-as-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-men-as-lovers/</guid>
      <description>INFJ men are complex, warm, and perceptive. They’re drawn to women who are intelligent, creative, and compassionate. While few INFJ men ever achieve perfect relationships, they always wish for them. This is a positive quality when they stay in a committed relationship but it works against them when they move from one woman to another, always seeking a partner who lives up to their ideals.
If you’re in a relationship with an INFJ male, your feelings won’t go unnoticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Women as Lovers</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-women-as-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-women-as-lovers/</guid>
      <description>The INFJ female is an intense, passionate woman. She is drawn to the opposite sex, but few of them turn out to be long-term partners because they’re the wrong type. Still, the woman keeps trying. If she finally meets a man with a compatible personality and finds him moderately attractive, the connection usually strengthens.
The INFJ woman is compassionate, intelligent, and creative. While she longs for a perfect relationship, she seldom achieves her goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJs smile</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infjs-smile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infjs-smile/</guid>
      <description>In days when it seems hard to be an INFJ, it’s worth looking at some of the qualities that come with this Myers-Briggs personality type. We may be only 1 percent of the population, but we have a lot of work to do in the world.
Actively contribute to the welfare of others.
Are patient and gentle with others but often hard on ourselves.
Lead others quietly; not imposing our will but influencing them behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets ISFJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-isfj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-isfj/</guid>
      <description>INFJs and ISFJs are alike in many ways. Both are introverted, feeling, and judging. They differ only on the intuitive/sensing (N/S) dimension of the Myers-Briggs Inventory. Both types put much of their energy into helping others. They share a need to make the world a better place. People can count on them in times of trouble.
Although both have high ideals, they’re modest about them. They prefer to make their values apparent in their actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Hard To Be an INFJ—The Rarest Myers-Briggs Personality Type</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj/</guid>
      <description>Myers-Briggs Inventory
Isabel Myers and her mother, Katharine Briggs—both psychologists— developed the Myers-Briggs Personality Inventory more than fifty years ago.
Carl Jung They were looking for a way to classify different types of personalities and describe them using the theories of Carl Jung, the famous Swiss psychoanalyst. They wanted to create a tool to help people understand themselves and others.
The Myers-Briggs Inventory was first published in 1975. Its practical applications have been expanding ever since—in schools and colleges, business, counselors’ offices, and other settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Hard To Be an INFJ: The Author’s Personal Story</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj-the-authors-personal-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj-the-authors-personal-story/</guid>
      <description>Since posting “It’s Hard To Be an INFJ” on this blog, I’ve received hundreds of e-mails from other INFJs. Their main theme has been how disconnected they’ve felt surrounded by extraverts and more sensible, earthbound types. Their posts and my responses appear after that blog.
This is my personal account of what it feels like to be an INFJ.
Growing up
As a child, I felt like an outsider. I’ve felt this way most of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perceiving vs. Judging—The Dating Game</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/perceiving-vs-judging-the-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/perceiving-vs-judging-the-conflict/</guid>
      <description>Perceiving (P) and Judging (J) are a set of opposite traits on the Myers-Briggs Personality Inventory. They are called the attitude traits. The other three sets are Extraversion vs. Introversion (energy), Sensing vs. Intuition (information-processing), and Thinking vs. Feeling (decision-making). Differences in the J-P function may cause considerable friction among opposites—particularly between the Judger, for example, who is always on time for appointments and the Perceiver who always arrives late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensors vs. Intuitives—The Dating Game</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/sensors-vs-intuitives-the-dating-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/sensors-vs-intuitives-the-dating-game/</guid>
      <description>In the dating game, the Sensing and Intuitive Myers-Briggs preferences can be a source of excitement and, at the same time, confusion.
Sensors are realistic about dating partners. They judge other people by what they do and say. Being grounded in objective reality, they aren’t impressed by phony facades or bragging. They clearly see the good and the bad in the here and now. Intuitives, with their active imaginations, are more titillated by the possibilities in their minds than what’s actually taking place in the present.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
