<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>relationship on BLOG : hb_beacon</title>
    <link>https://klayu.github.io/hb_beacon/tag/relationship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in relationship on BLOG : hb_beacon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://klayu.github.io/hb_beacon/tag/relationship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Men as Lovers</title>
      <link>https://klayu.github.io/hb_beacon/wp/infj-men-as-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klayu.github.io/hb_beacon/wp/infj-men-as-lovers/</guid>
      <description>INFJ men are complex, warm, and perceptive. They’re drawn to women who are intelligent, creative, and compassionate. While few INFJ men ever achieve perfect relationships, they always wish for them. This is a positive quality when they stay in a committed relationship but it works against them when they move from one woman to another, always seeking a partner who lives up to their ideals.
If you’re in a relationship with an INFJ male, your feelings won’t go unnoticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perceiving vs. Judging—The Dating Game</title>
      <link>https://klayu.github.io/hb_beacon/wp/perceiving-vs-judging-the-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klayu.github.io/hb_beacon/wp/perceiving-vs-judging-the-conflict/</guid>
      <description>Perceiving (P) and Judging (J) are a set of opposite traits on the Myers-Briggs Personality Inventory. They are called the attitude traits. The other three sets are Extraversion vs. Introversion (energy), Sensing vs. Intuition (information-processing), and Thinking vs. Feeling (decision-making). Differences in the J-P function may cause considerable friction among opposites—particularly between the Judger, for example, who is always on time for appointments and the Perceiver who always arrives late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensors vs. Intuitives—The Dating Game</title>
      <link>https://klayu.github.io/hb_beacon/wp/sensors-vs-intuitives-the-dating-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klayu.github.io/hb_beacon/wp/sensors-vs-intuitives-the-dating-game/</guid>
      <description>In the dating game, the Sensing and Intuitive Myers-Briggs preferences can be a source of excitement and, at the same time, confusion.
Sensors are realistic about dating partners. They judge other people by what they do and say. Being grounded in objective reality, they aren’t impressed by phony facades or bragging. They clearly see the good and the bad in the here and now. Intuitives, with their active imaginations, are more titillated by the possibilities in their minds than what’s actually taking place in the present.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
