<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BeaconStreet USA</title>
    <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BeaconStreet USA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 01:09:48 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who Was Donald Trump’s Mother? Mary Anne MacLeod Trump</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/mary-anne-macleod-trump-donald-trumps-mother/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/mary-anne-macleod-trump-donald-trumps-mother/</guid>
      <description>The Foundations of Greatness: Exploring the Early Life and Background of Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Parents The story of a prominent figure often finds its roots in the experiences and influences of their parents. Donald J. Trump, the 45th President of the United States, is no exception. To truly understand the man who became a global business magnate and political leader, we must delve into the early life and background of his parents, Frederick Christ Trump and Mary Anne MacLeod Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extroverted Animals And Their Myers Briggs Personality Types!</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/extraverted-animals-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/extraverted-animals-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types/</guid>
      <description>The Extroverted Myers-Briggs Personality Type: Animals, Traits, and Identification
The Myers-Briggs Type Indicator (MBTI) is a popular psychological assessment tool that categorizes individuals into 16 distinct personality types based on their preferences and tendencies. One of these types is the Extroverted personality, which is characterized by a preference for social interaction, energy from the external world, and a focus on the present. In this article, we will explore the Extroverted Myers-Briggs Personality Type, some of the animals that have this type, and how you can notice it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introverted Reserved Animals and their myers briggs personality types</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/introverted-animals-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/introverted-animals-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types/</guid>
      <description>The Introverted Myers Briggs Personality : Shy And Quiet Type
Exploring Animal Examples and Identifying Traits
The Myers Briggs Personality Type Indicator (MBTI) is a popular tool used to categorize individuals based on their psychological preferences. The MBTI is based on the work of psychiatrist Carl Jung and was developed by Katharine Briggs and Isabel Briggs Myers. It categorizes individuals into 16 different personality types, each with their own unique characteristics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ISTJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-istj-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 02:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-istj-2/</guid>
      <description>It’s fair to say that any two people with this combination of Myers-Briggs traits are likely to have adjustment problems if they’re to function smoothly together. While they are joined in their preference for privacy (introversion), this isn’t enough to make them compatible. Both have a preference for judging, as well, but they use the function in dissimilar ways due to their other trait differences.
The INFJ is introverted (I), intuitive (N), feeling (F), and judging (J).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Distribution by Myers-Briggs Type</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-type-and-career-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-type-and-career-choice/</guid>
      <description>A 14-year study of thousands of Americans in various careers shows that different Myers-Biggs types have different preferences and skills relating to the jobs they take. When the data were analyzed at the end of the 14 years, researchers found that people of various Myers-Briggs categories most often held the following jobs listed below.
Career Distribution by Myers-Briggs Type
ISTJ: Administrators in schools, industry, and health care, dentists, police and detectives,auditors and accountants ISFJ: Nurses, clerical supervisors, preschool teachers, librarians, health technicians INFJ: Education consultants, clergy, physicians, media specialists, teachers (English, art, drama) INTJ: Lawyers, scientists, computer systems analysts, chemical engineers, university teachers ISTP: Farmers, mechanics and repairers, electrical technicians, engineers, dental hygienists ISFP: Storekeepers and stock clerks, nurses, dental assistants, bookkeepers, mechanics and repairers INFP: Psychiatrists and psychologists, writers, artists, and editors, teachers, social workers, musicians and composers INTP: Writers, artists and entertainers, computer programmers, social scientists ESTP: Marketing personnel, police and detectives, managers and administrators, retail salespeople, auditors ESFP: child care workers, receptionists, salespeople, religious workers, teachers (preschool) ENFP: Rehabilitation counselors, teachers (art and drama), writers, artists, entertainers, psychologists, clergy ENTP: Photographers, marketing personnel, salespeople, journalists, computer systems analysts ESTJ: Teachers, school administrators, surgeons, factory and site supervisors, lawyers ESFJ: Medical secretaries, clergy, nurses, home economists, hairdressers and cosmetologists ENFJ: Clergy, teachers, actors and entertainers, writers and artists, consultants ENTJ: Lawyers, managers, mortgage brokers, administrators (computer systems and education), scientists The study data do not indicate which careers are best for certain types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Depression Profiles—INFJ vs. INFP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/depression-profiles-infj-vs-infp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/depression-profiles-infj-vs-infp/</guid>
      <description>The Myers-Briggs types INFJ and INFP are affected by depression more than most other types. Both are Introverted (I), intuitive (N), and feeling (F). This means that they have a compassionate nature, see the underlying meaning of events around them and have trouble shielding themselves from the pain of others, particularly in the face of indifference of others. They puzzle about why they are so powerless to change things. They realize that they were meant for greater things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous People and Their Myers-Briggs Personality Types—Part 1: The Extraverts</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-1-the-extraverts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-1-the-extraverts/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, Myers-Briggs experts have analyzed many famous people to make educated guesses of their personality types. While most celebrities, past and present, have never taken a personality test, psychologists who are knowledgeable about typology believe they know what the outcomes would be.
Most politicians, entertainers, and leaders of large organizations are extraverts. Introverts are usually deep thinkers, complex individuals who can be charming in public but are private in their personal lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous People and Their Myers-Briggs Personality Types: Part 2, the Introverts</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-2-the-introverts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-2-the-introverts/</guid>
      <description>The Myers-Briggs personality test has been used to analyze many famous people. While most celebrities, past and present, have never taken a personality test, psychologists who are knowledgeable about typology believe they know what the outcomes would be.
Introverts are usually deep thinkers, complex individuals who can be charming in public but are private in their personal lives. Introverts aren’t easily categorized or put in boxes. Most politicians, entertainers, and leaders of large organizations are extraverts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ meets ENTJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-entj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-entj/</guid>
      <description>INFJs and ENTJs are on the same wavelength in many ways. They enjoy spending time together and sharing creative, stimulating conversations. Superficial topics bore them. Both have excellent intuition and can size people up accurately on short acquaintance. They share the ability to comprehend complex situations that baffle others.
While the two types can become close friends, INFJs should be mindful of the ENTJ’s rough edges. This type can be blunt, with little tolerance for mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ESFJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-esfj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-esfj/</guid>
      <description>When an INFJ and ESFJ are drawn to each other, the attraction becomes obvious fairly quickly— although the ESFJ is usually the more transparent of the two and is likely to make the first overtures. INFJs are generally cautious until they’re sure of a relationship.
ESFJs are generous and outgoing, giving without any thought of return. If someone expresses a need, they’re among the first to try to satisfy it. They place a high value on harmony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ESFP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-esfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-esfp/</guid>
      <description>What happens when an INFJ meets an ESFP? Is there an instant attraction? Do they repel each other like two magnets?
Looking at their personality traits, you’d think they have little in common. When an early attraction persists, it’s cause for wonder. Usually, the bond is associated with their shared feeling (F) trait.
Introversion (I) vs. Extraversion (E)
The first big difference lies in the INFJ’s need for privacy vs. the ESFP’s preference for social contact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ESTJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-estj-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-estj-2/</guid>
      <description>All things considered, the attraction between the ESTJs and INFJs isn’t surprising. Because ESTJs are conventional people, they prefer colorful partners to make their lives more interesting. They aren’t drawn to other ESTJs. INFJs have creative minds and supply the friendly, playful traits ESTJs are missing. The INFJ, in turn, is rewarded by an appreciative audience.
An INFJ may find ESTJ friends too direct and outspoken. They tend to overlook polite ways of dealing with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ meets INTP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-intp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-intp/</guid>
      <description>INFJs are often drawn to INTPs because of their intelligence and ability to apply logic to every situation. Eventually, though, INFJs tend to find most INTPs distant because of their unemotional approach to life. The INTP is attracted to INFJs because of their compassion and spontaneity. But the qualities that drew them to an INFJ in the first place can eventually get on their nerves. To them, it’s sloppy to let feelings override logic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ meets ISFJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-isfj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-isfj/</guid>
      <description>INFJs and ISFJs are alike in many ways. They’re introverted, feeling, and judging. They differ only on the intuitive/sensing dimension of the Myers-Briggs Inventory. Both types put much of their energy into helping others and share a drive to make the world a better place. People can count on them in times of trouble.
Although INFJs and ISFJs have high ideals, they’re modest about them. They prefer to make their values apparent in their actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ISFP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-isfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-isfp/</guid>
      <description>As one of sixteen Myers-Briggs types, the INFJ is introverted (I), intuitive (N), feeling (F), and judging (J). A little different from the ISFP—who shares the introverted (I) and feeling (F) traits but not the intuitive (N) and judging (J) traits.
Both have a need for some privacy to collect themselves and regroup. If the INFJ says to an ISFP partner, “I think I’ll go out and straighten up the garage,” the ISFP is likely to interpret this as a need for time alone and say “Good idea,” rather than “Want me to come?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ISTP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-istp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-istp/</guid>
      <description>It’s obvious looking at the letters I-N-F-J and I-S-T-P that these two Myers-Briggs personality types are very different. The only trait they have in common is their introversion. Both types enjoy privacy. They find meaning not from superficial experiences but from their contemplation of them.
Sensing vs. Intuition
Because ISTPs rely on their sensing preference more than their intuition, they are driven to understand how things work. They usually have good eye-hand coordination, which makes them skilled at fixing things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Men as Lovers</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-men-as-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-men-as-lovers/</guid>
      <description>INFJ men are complex, warm, and perceptive. They’re drawn to women who are intelligent, creative, and compassionate. While few INFJ men ever achieve perfect relationships, they always wish for them. This is a positive quality when they stay in a committed relationship but it works against them when they move from one woman to another, always seeking a partner who lives up to their ideals.
If you’re in a relationship with an INFJ male, your feelings won’t go unnoticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Women as Lovers</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-women-as-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-women-as-lovers/</guid>
      <description>The INFJ female is an intense, passionate woman. She is drawn to the opposite sex, but few of them turn out to be long-term partners because they’re the wrong type. Still, the woman keeps trying. If she finally meets a man with a compatible personality and finds him moderately attractive, the connection usually strengthens.
The INFJ woman is compassionate, intelligent, and creative. While she longs for a perfect relationship, she seldom achieves her goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJs smile</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infjs-smile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infjs-smile/</guid>
      <description>In days when it seems hard to be an INFJ, it’s worth looking at some of the qualities that come with this Myers-Briggs personality type. We may be only 1 percent of the population, but we have a lot of work to do in the world.
Actively contribute to the welfare of others.
Are patient and gentle with others but often hard on ourselves.
Lead others quietly; not imposing our will but influencing them behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets ISFJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-isfj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-isfj/</guid>
      <description>INFJs and ISFJs are alike in many ways. Both are introverted, feeling, and judging. They differ only on the intuitive/sensing (N/S) dimension of the Myers-Briggs Inventory. Both types put much of their energy into helping others. They share a need to make the world a better place. People can count on them in times of trouble.
Although both have high ideals, they’re modest about them. They prefer to make their values apparent in their actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Hard To Be an INFJ—The Rarest Myers-Briggs Personality Type</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj/</guid>
      <description>Myers-Briggs Inventory
Isabel Myers and her mother, Katharine Briggs—both psychologists— developed the Myers-Briggs Personality Inventory more than fifty years ago.
Carl Jung They were looking for a way to classify different types of personalities and describe them using the theories of Carl Jung, the famous Swiss psychoanalyst. They wanted to create a tool to help people understand themselves and others.
The Myers-Briggs Inventory was first published in 1975. Its practical applications have been expanding ever since—in schools and colleges, business, counselors’ offices, and other settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Hard To Be an INFJ: The Author’s Personal Story</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj-the-authors-personal-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj-the-authors-personal-story/</guid>
      <description>Since posting “It’s Hard To Be an INFJ” on this blog, I’ve received hundreds of e-mails from other INFJs. Their main theme has been how disconnected they’ve felt surrounded by extraverts and more sensible, earthbound types. Their posts and my responses appear after that blog.
This is my personal account of what it feels like to be an INFJ.
Growing up
As a child, I felt like an outsider. I’ve felt this way most of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perceiving vs. Judging—The Dating Game</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/perceiving-vs-judging-the-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/perceiving-vs-judging-the-conflict/</guid>
      <description>Perceiving (P) and Judging (J) are a set of opposite traits on the Myers-Briggs Personality Inventory. They are called the attitude traits. The other three sets are Extraversion vs. Introversion (energy), Sensing vs. Intuition (information-processing), and Thinking vs. Feeling (decision-making). Differences in the J-P function may cause considerable friction among opposites—particularly between the Judger, for example, who is always on time for appointments and the Perceiver who always arrives late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensors vs. Intuitives—The Dating Game</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/sensors-vs-intuitives-the-dating-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/sensors-vs-intuitives-the-dating-game/</guid>
      <description>In the dating game, the Sensing and Intuitive Myers-Briggs preferences can be a source of excitement and, at the same time, confusion.
Sensors are realistic about dating partners. They judge other people by what they do and say. Being grounded in objective reality, they aren’t impressed by phony facades or bragging. They clearly see the good and the bad in the here and now. Intuitives, with their active imaginations, are more titillated by the possibilities in their minds than what’s actually taking place in the present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introverted Disney Characters and Their Personality Types: Part 1 of a Two-Part Series</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/introverted-disney-characters-and-their-personality-types-part-1-of-a-two-part-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/introverted-disney-characters-and-their-personality-types-part-1-of-a-two-part-series/</guid>
      <description>Introverted Disney Characters and Their Personality Types: Part 1 of a Two-Part Series
Why do Disney characters hold such a special place in our hearts?
Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s because we find a reflection of ourselves in their stories, particularly in the introverted characters like Jiminy Cricket, Alice in Wonderland, Pocahontas, and Merlin. For those who know their Myers-Briggs personality types, you might discover a connection to some of these beloved figures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous Infjs The Good And The Evil!</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-infjs-the-good-and-the-evil/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-infjs-the-good-and-the-evil/</guid>
      <description>Famous Good amd Evil INFJ people
INFJ is one of the 16 personality types identified by the Myers-Briggs Type Indicator (MBTI). INFJs are often described as insightful, caring, and creative individuals who place great importance on personal values and emotional connections with others. They are also known as &amp;ldquo;The Advocate&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;The Counselor.&amp;rdquo; When famous INFJs worked for good, they were positive forces in the world. When they turned evil, they became dangerous and desperate people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You a Sensor or an Intuitive?</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/are-you-a-sensor-or-an-intuitive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/are-you-a-sensor-or-an-intuitive/</guid>
      <description>More confusion probably exists regarding Sensors (S) and Intuitives (N) than any other type. Extraverts (E) and Introverts (I) are easy to tell apart. So are Thinkers (T) and Feelers (F). The labels themselves are giveaways. Perceiving (P) and Judging (J) require a bit of observation to figure out. Is the person usually late for deadlines and appointments? Does he or she avoid making final decisions on things as long as possible?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Droid Addiction</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/droid-addiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/droid-addiction/</guid>
      <description>At an upscale restaurant with two women friends the other night, I watched one play with her android nonstop during dinner. She showed us over 100 photos taken with several cameras on the device. She pulled up Google Earth and other apps and played with them. The conversation was never allowed to stray far from her ‘droid.
This woman is in her mid-forties; the other friend and I are 87 and 79, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Cost of Meat</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/environmental-cost-of-meat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/environmental-cost-of-meat/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. could feed 800 million people with grain that livestock consume say Cornell University ecologist researchers. If the grain were exported, it would increase the U.S. trade balance by $80 billion per year.
The American system of feeding livestock grain rather than allowing cattle to feed on pastureland consumes resources far disproportionate to the yield. What’s more it accelerates soil erosion, uses huge amounts of water, and affects world food supply in a negative way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extraverted Disney Characters and Their Personality Types: Part 2 of a Two-Part Series</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/extraverted-disney-characters-and-their-personality-types-part-2-of-a-two-part-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/extraverted-disney-characters-and-their-personality-types-part-2-of-a-two-part-series/</guid>
      <description>Why do we love Disney characters so much? What is it about their stories that touches our hearts?
We see reflections of own personalities in characters like Jiminy Cricket, Alice in Wonderland, Pocahontas, and even Merlin. If you know your Myers-Briggs personality type, maybe you can relate to some of them. This blog tells you about the extraverts (E) among Disney’s colorful animated characters
ENTJ: Buzz Lightyear
Buzz Lightyear, a toy space ranger in “Toy Story,” is known for his bravery and courage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extraverts in Retirement</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/extraverts-in-retirement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/extraverts-in-retirement/</guid>
      <description>With advancing age, their Myers-Briggs personality scores of people can change, but not by much. Extreme scores on one or more traits tend to soften and move toward the middle. The ESTJ who had a strong thinking (T) score is likely to move a little toward Feeling, with stronger emotional elements in their personality than previously. This blog describes the eight Extraverted (E) types in their retirement years. Every combination of traits is represented, making eight in all—Extraverted plus Sensing (S) or Intuition (N), Thinking (T) or Feeling (F), and Perceiving (P) or.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally, an Updated Version of the Big Book of AA for Today’s Reader</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/ez-big-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/ez-big-book/</guid>
      <description>The EZ Big Book of Alcoholics Anonymous is a paragraph by paragraph “translation” of the original Alcoholics Anonymous—known to AA members as the Big Book—published by AA founder Bill Wilson in the 1930s. The EZ Big Book carries the AA message to readers who find the original text hard to digest for any reason. The language is gender neutral and embraces modern lifestyles. The references to spirituality are more inclusive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Seduce an INFJ Woman</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/how-to-seduce-an-infj-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/how-to-seduce-an-infj-woman/</guid>
      <description>The way that men and women express themselves in love matches differs widely. Much of the difference can be traced back to Myers-Briggs type. Some types are more sexual than others. Both INFJ men and women are intense and creative in their love lives.
Let’s say you’ve met an INFJ woman and she fascinates you. After initial contact, you ask her out, and she’s agreed to a date. You’ve concluded that this is not a throwaway date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ENFJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-enfj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-enfj/</guid>
      <description>People of the INFJ and ENFJ Myers-Briggs types usually make compatible friends and partners. It makes sense when you look at their shared traits: intuition, feeling, and judging. The two types differ only in their tendencies toward introversion and extraversion, and that’s not all bad. The introverted INFJ is likely to encourage the ENFJ to spend time together so they can enjoy each other’s company in private. The ENFJ, in turn, promotes participation in social activities and group events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ENTP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-entp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-entp/</guid>
      <description>INFJs usually get along well with ENTPs. This may be surprising when one considers that they have only one Myers-Briggs trait in common—intuition (N).
With their tendency toward introversion (I), INFJs are reserved and shy. Extraverted (E) ENTPs are gregarious and outgoing. As a feeling type (F), INFJs base their decisions on emotional factors, mainly the impact their choices will have on others. More rational ENTPs, with their thinking (T) preference, make decisions based on hard facts, not feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ESTP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-estp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-estp/</guid>
      <description>When an INFJ meets an ESTP, some special chemistry must be at work for them to enjoy time together. These Myers-Briggs types are exact opposites. The INFJ (I) is introverted—a private person. The ESTP (E) is sociable and outgoing. INFJs rely more on intuition (N) than concrete facts to reach conclusions. ESTPs use their sensing (S) function to get information from the immediate environment. INFJs take action based on their feeling (F) function, evaluating the impact of their decisions on others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets INFP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-infp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-infp/</guid>
      <description>INFP (introverted-intuitive-feeling-perceiving) and INFJ (introverted-intuitive-feeling-judging) types are a lot alike. They have rich inner lives and treasure their solitude. Also, their intuition is highly developed, giving them the ability to see what’s going on under the surface. They understand why people do the things they do. Because they see through facades and games, deceivers and players can seldom fool them for long. INFPs and INFJs examine every piece of evidence for its fundamental truth and then seek the wider context into which it fits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introverts at Risk</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/introverts-at-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/introverts-at-risk/</guid>
      <description>Each of the sixteen Myers-Briggs types is unique and different. Some types are outgoing and gregarious, while others treasure their privacy. Some are serious and others are fun-loving. Some are warm and giving and others are cool-headed and objective. A few of the types have similar descriptions. That’s because they have several traits in common. For example, the INFP is much like the INFJ because each is introverted (I), intuitive (N), and Feeling (F).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Romance in the Air?  INFJ Meets INFP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infp/</guid>
      <description>INFP and INFJ types are alike in many ways. Both types are introverted (I), intuitive (N), and feeling (F). They have rich inner lives and treasure their solitude. Their intuition is highly developed, giving them the ability to see what’s going on under the surface. They understand why people do the things they do. Because they see through facades and games, deceivers and players can seldom fool them for long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets ENFP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-enfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-enfp/</guid>
      <description>Myers-Briggs personality traits have a lot to do with the potential for romance, friendship, and working relationships. They’re important in family life, too. Romance has a better chance of lasting between lovers of similar Myers-Briggs types. Siblings of the same personality type are likely to get along better than those of very different types.
People of the Myers-Briggs INFJ personality type share some characteristics with the ENFP type, but not others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets INFJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infj/</guid>
      <description>When two INFJs find each other, they’re lucky. After all, only one percent of the population is the INFJ type. INFJs are kind, generous, and helpful to others. When friends or even strangers are in trouble, INFJs hurry to the rescue. They’re ready to offer creative solutions or hands-on support.
As friends or partners, each can depend on the other to behave with integrity—whatever the setting. Their actions match their ideals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets ISTP</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-istp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-istp/</guid>
      <description>If you’re an INFJ, you may find yourself drawn to ISTPs. They’re quietly competent, people of few words who make every utterance worth listening to. They pay attention. They have emotional control. How refreshing!
INFJs and ISTPs have very different personalities. The only trait they have in common is introversion (I). Because both are private people, they prefer thinking about things to talking about them. They’re quiet, but their minds are always busy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johari’s Window</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/joharis-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/joharis-window/</guid>
      <description>The Johari Window is a psychological model that was designed for use in self-help groups to help members become more intimate with their peers, while at the same time learning to become more honest with themselves. The concept helps people understand the extent of their self-awareness compared to how others perceive them. It was developed in the mid-1950s by two psychologists who combined their first names to label the idea: Joseph Luft and Harrington Ingham (Jo-Hari).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types of Children—Extraverted Kids</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-extraverted-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-extraverted-kids/</guid>
      <description>Do children’s personalities remain consistent over the years? If they’re happy babies, will they be happy adults? Or do experiences early in life play a major role in what they become?
Psychologists believe that both are true. According to experts in Myers-Briggs personality testing, people are born with certain traits or tendencies. Their attitudes and behaviors may be modified by the environment over time, but they don’t disappear entirely. The child who likes to play catch and climb trees will probably be an athletic grown-up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types of Children—Part 1: Introverted Kids</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-part-1-introverted-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-part-1-introverted-kids/</guid>
      <description>If your baby comes home from the hospital quiet and easy-going, will the peace last? What about the toddler who enjoys nothing more than turning the pages of a book, while another is scaling every surface in sight? Will their personalities change over the years?
Parents who dreamed of their child becoming a celebrated athlete may be disappointed when he or she prefers staying inside taking a clock apart to playing outdoors with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Gainesville Ketamine Infusion Clinic</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/new-gainesville-ketamine-infusion-clinic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/new-gainesville-ketamine-infusion-clinic/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Shy and Introvert Disney Characters: A Journey Through the Quiet and Reserved
Florida Mind Health Center for Ketamine Therapy is Gainesville’s new—and only—ketamine infusion therapy center. Located just off Millhopper Road near NW Thirty-Ninth Street, the clinic offers revolutionary, fast-acting methods bringing comprehensive treatments for a number of resistant mood disorders and pain-related conditions—most notably, depression and anxiety. Many patients experience improvement after just one session, making ketamine infusions an option superior to traditional treatment methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year’s Resolutions for INFJs</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/am/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/am/</guid>
      <description>We INFJs, like the other fifteen Myers-Briggs types, have our weak spots—vulnerabilities that sometimes bring us into conflict with others or cause personal problems. To be healthy and fully functional, we need to take advantage of all eight Myers-Briggs traits: introvert (I), extravert (E), sensing (S), intuitive (N), thinking (T), feeling (F), judging (J), and perceiving (P).
I am a good example:
As an INFJ
I tend to prefer solitude or the company of only one or two friends (I).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prevalence of INFJs in the General Population</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/prevalence-of-infjs-in-the-general-population/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/prevalence-of-infjs-in-the-general-population/</guid>
      <description>According to researchers, the INFJ Myers-Briggs type occurs in about 1% of the population—the lowest prevalence of any type. Studies vary regarding the exact percentages of the 16 types, but INFJs always walk away with the prize for the most rare.
The downside of being an INFJ is that there are few people out there with whom they can relate deeply. Also, they don’t fit into social norms because their qualities are unusual and, to some people, unsettling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSTD in INFJ Women After Sexual Assault</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/pstd-in-infj-women-after-sexual-assault/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/pstd-in-infj-women-after-sexual-assault/</guid>
      <description>Several readers have asked whether INFJ women are more prone than other Myers-Briggs types to getting PTSD after sexual assault. The readers have themselves been victims of rape. I’d never considered this idea before, but I think they’re onto something.
In my opinion, INFJs tend to have stronger emotional reactions to events than other types. Sexual assault is a particularly damaging experience and PTSD is common among rape victims. Many suffer for months, years or even a lifetime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanja Askani–Creator of the New Bambi and Thumper</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/tanja-askani-creator-of-the-new-bambi-and-thumper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/tanja-askani-creator-of-the-new-bambi-and-thumper/</guid>
      <description>Return of Bambi and Thumper
Tanja Askani, a Czech author, photographer, and animal scientist living in Germany, has disseminated a series of Bambi-Thumper photos that have gone viral on the internet. People find them adorable. When I received the series in my e-mail, I thought they looked too good to be true. They were.
After downloading the photos and examining them in zoom view, I found clear evidence that every photo had been altered substantially.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Blame Game</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/the-blame-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/the-blame-game/</guid>
      <description>Are you prone to playing the “blame game” when something goes wrong in your life? Do you have friends or relatives who do it? There are lots of synonyms for “blame”—for example, “hold responsible or accountable”, “condemn,” “accuse,” “find guilty,” “assign fault,” or even “point the finger.”
If you automatically blame your partner when you fall on the kitchen linoleum, you might accuse him or her of not keeping the kitchen floor clean—ignoring the fact that you were clumsy because you were hurried and careless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lord’s Prayer in A.A. Meetings</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/the-lords-prayer-in-a-a-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/the-lords-prayer-in-a-a-meetings/</guid>
      <description>In my AA home group, we start meetings by reading from the Big Book: “AA is not allied with any sect, denomination, politics, organization, or institution.” Then we end with the Lord’s Prayer.
There’s something wrong here. The Lord’s Prayer is from the New Testament of the Christian Bible (Matthew 6:9-13). As a Christian Internet source states. “Through this prayer, Jesus invited us to approach God as Father. Indeed, the Lord’s Prayer has been called a summary of the Christian gospel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timex or Rolex?</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/timex-or-rolex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/timex-or-rolex/</guid>
      <description>Timex, hands down. Please understand, I don’t have a grudge against Rolex watches because I can’t afford one–although, at an average price of $8000, it would pinch a little. I like the way the Timex looks–modest, practical, tasteful. It doesn’t shout, “Look at me! I’M RICH!” Also, a Timex watch is not a fussy gadget. It’s a workhorse.
Lighted dial
Timex watches have lighted dials. Rolex watches do not. Eight grand and no lighted dial?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Waits, I Love You</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/tom-waits-i-love-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/tom-waits-i-love-you/</guid>
      <description>Only this year, after my 78th birthday, did I discover Tom Waits. Now I’m in love and it’s too late. Tom is probably happily married and too old for this, anyway. I’m not married, but I’m sure too old.
I’m spellbound by Tom’s gravelly, singing voice In YouTube videos, I watch him dance on the stage like a kid, leaping into the air with the mike.
You know that Tom Waits loves women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unconditional Love</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/unconditional-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/unconditional-love/</guid>
      <description>Animals are such agreeable friends. They ask no questions. They pass no criticisms. —George Eliot
If you have a dog or cat you’re close to, you know what unconditional love is. You give it freely and you get it in return.
We might do well to apply the same principle to our human companions, appreciating the bond of love between us and avoiding judgments.
Affirmation: Today, I will accept the people in my life as they are, not as I think they should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When INFJs Go Bad</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/when-infjs-go-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/when-infjs-go-bad/</guid>
      <description>When INFJs are on track, they’re creative and insightful. They’re almost clairvoyant. In addition, they’re compassionate and generous. They are protectors of the weak. As idealists, they have strong values. And they get a lot done. While they prefer private time to socializing, they use their solitude productively. INFJs can be depended on to come through—and to come through on time.
How can they miss? Any Myers-Briggs type can overuse or abuse one or more traits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Study Habits</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/your-study-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/your-study-habits/</guid>
      <description>In fifty years of solitary work—researching and writing—I’ve discovered that some environments put me in a more productive frame of mind than others. When the conditions aren’t “ideal” for me, I get distracted easily. Disarray puts me in a jumpy mood and I don’t stay on task very long. A review of the literature suggests that I’m not alone.
According to behavioral scientists, several conditions influence your motivation to study:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subsrcibe</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/subsrcibe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/subsrcibe/</guid>
      <description>Please subsrcibe to get notified when I post new blog articles.
Email Subscribe </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/thankyou/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to take a moment to express my deepest gratitude for subscribing to my blog. Your decision to join our community of readers means a lot to me, and I am truly honored that you have chosen to stay connected with my work.
As a blogger, I am constantly inspired by my readers, and I am excited to have the opportunity to share my thoughts and ideas with you. Your subscription serves as a reminder that my work is meaningful and valuable, and it motivates me to continue producing high-quality content that resonates with you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
