<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ISTJ on BeaconStreet USA</title>
    <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/tag/istj/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ISTJ on BeaconStreet USA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/tag/istj/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Career Distribution by Myers-Briggs Type</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-type-and-career-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-type-and-career-choice/</guid>
      <description>A 14-year study of thousands of Americans in various careers shows that different Myers-Biggs types have different preferences and skills relating to the jobs they take. When the data were analyzed at the end of the 14 years, researchers found that people of various Myers-Briggs categories most often held the following jobs listed below.
Career Distribution by Myers-Briggs Type
ISTJ: Administrators in schools, industry, and health care, dentists, police and detectives,auditors and accountants ISFJ: Nurses, clerical supervisors, preschool teachers, librarians, health technicians INFJ: Education consultants, clergy, physicians, media specialists, teachers (English, art, drama) INTJ: Lawyers, scientists, computer systems analysts, chemical engineers, university teachers ISTP: Farmers, mechanics and repairers, electrical technicians, engineers, dental hygienists ISFP: Storekeepers and stock clerks, nurses, dental assistants, bookkeepers, mechanics and repairers INFP: Psychiatrists and psychologists, writers, artists, and editors, teachers, social workers, musicians and composers INTP: Writers, artists and entertainers, computer programmers, social scientists ESTP: Marketing personnel, police and detectives, managers and administrators, retail salespeople, auditors ESFP: child care workers, receptionists, salespeople, religious workers, teachers (preschool) ENFP: Rehabilitation counselors, teachers (art and drama), writers, artists, entertainers, psychologists, clergy ENTP: Photographers, marketing personnel, salespeople, journalists, computer systems analysts ESTJ: Teachers, school administrators, surgeons, factory and site supervisors, lawyers ESFJ: Medical secretaries, clergy, nurses, home economists, hairdressers and cosmetologists ENFJ: Clergy, teachers, actors and entertainers, writers and artists, consultants ENTJ: Lawyers, managers, mortgage brokers, administrators (computer systems and education), scientists The study data do not indicate which careers are best for certain types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous People and Their Myers-Briggs Personality Types—Part 1: The Extraverts</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-1-the-extraverts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-1-the-extraverts/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, Myers-Briggs experts have analyzed many famous people to make educated guesses of their personality types. While most celebrities, past and present, have never taken a personality test, psychologists who are knowledgeable about typology believe they know what the outcomes would be.
Most politicians, entertainers, and leaders of large organizations are extraverts. Introverts are usually deep thinkers, complex individuals who can be charming in public but are private in their personal lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous People and Their Myers-Briggs Personality Types: Part 2, the Introverts</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-2-the-introverts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-2-the-introverts/</guid>
      <description>The Myers-Briggs personality test has been used to analyze many famous people. While most celebrities, past and present, have never taken a personality test, psychologists who are knowledgeable about typology believe they know what the outcomes would be.
Introverts are usually deep thinkers, complex individuals who can be charming in public but are private in their personal lives. Introverts aren’t easily categorized or put in boxes. Most politicians, entertainers, and leaders of large organizations are extraverts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
