<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>INFJ on BeaconStreet USA</title>
    <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/tag/infj/</link>
    <description>Recent content in INFJ on BeaconStreet USA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:10:48 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/tag/infj/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Famous People and Their Myers-Briggs Personality Types—Part 1: The Extraverts</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-1-the-extraverts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-1-the-extraverts/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, Myers-Briggs experts have analyzed many famous people to make educated guesses of their personality types. While most celebrities, past and present, have never taken a personality test, psychologists who are knowledgeable about typology believe they know what the outcomes would be.
Most politicians, entertainers, and leaders of large organizations are extraverts. Introverts are usually deep thinkers, complex individuals who can be charming in public but are private in their personal lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous Infjs The Good And The Evil!</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-infjs-the-good-and-the-evil/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-infjs-the-good-and-the-evil/</guid>
      <description>Famous Good amd Evil INFJ people
INFJ is one of the 16 personality types identified by the Myers-Briggs Type Indicator (MBTI). INFJs are often described as insightful, caring, and creative individuals who place great importance on personal values and emotional connections with others.
They are also known as &#34;The Advocate&#34; or &#34;The Counselor.&#34; When famous INFJs worked for good, they were positive forces in the world. When they turned evil, they became dangerous and desperate people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Distribution by Myers-Briggs Type</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-type-and-career-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/myers-briggs-type-and-career-choice/</guid>
      <description>A 14-year study of thousands of Americans in various careers shows that different Myers-Biggs types have different preferences and skills relating to the jobs they take. When the data were analyzed at the end of the 14 years, researchers found that people of various Myers-Briggs categories most often held the following jobs listed below.
Career Distribution by Myers-Briggs Type
ISTJ: Administrators in schools, industry, and health care, dentists, police and detectives,auditors and accountants ISFJ: Nurses, clerical supervisors, preschool teachers, librarians, health technicians INFJ: Education consultants, clergy, physicians, media specialists, teachers (English, art, drama) INTJ: Lawyers, scientists, computer systems analysts, chemical engineers, university teachers ISTP: Farmers, mechanics and repairers, electrical technicians, engineers, dental hygienists ISFP: Storekeepers and stock clerks, nurses, dental assistants, bookkeepers, mechanics and repairers INFP: Psychiatrists and psychologists, writers, artists, and editors, teachers, social workers, musicians and composers INTP: Writers, artists and entertainers, computer programmers, social scientists ESTP: Marketing personnel, police and detectives, managers and administrators, retail salespeople, auditors ESFP: child care workers, receptionists, salespeople, religious workers, teachers (preschool) ENFP: Rehabilitation counselors, teachers (art and drama), writers, artists, entertainers, psychologists, clergy ENTP: Photographers, marketing personnel, salespeople, journalists, computer systems analysts ESTJ: Teachers, school administrators, surgeons, factory and site supervisors, lawyers ESFJ: Medical secretaries, clergy, nurses, home economists, hairdressers and cosmetologists ENFJ: Clergy, teachers, actors and entertainers, writers and artists, consultants ENTJ: Lawyers, managers, mortgage brokers, administrators (computer systems and education), scientists The study data do not indicate which careers are best for certain types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous People and Their Myers-Briggs Personality Types: Part 2, the Introverts</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-2-the-introverts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-2-the-introverts/</guid>
      <description>The Myers-Briggs personality test has been used to analyze many famous people. While most celebrities, past and present, have never taken a personality test, psychologists who are knowledgeable about typology believe they know what the outcomes would be.
Introverts are usually deep thinkers, complex individuals who can be charming in public but are private in their personal lives. Introverts aren’t easily categorized or put in boxes. Most politicians, entertainers, and leaders of large organizations are extraverts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ meets ISFJ</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-isfj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-meets-isfj/</guid>
      <description>INFJs and ISFJs are alike in many ways. They’re introverted, feeling, and judging. They differ only on the intuitive/sensing dimension of the Myers-Briggs Inventory. Both types put much of their energy into helping others and share a drive to make the world a better place. People can count on them in times of trouble.
Although INFJs and ISFJs have high ideals, they’re modest about them. They prefer to make their values apparent in their actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Men as Lovers</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-men-as-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-men-as-lovers/</guid>
      <description>INFJ men are complex, warm, and perceptive. They’re drawn to women who are intelligent, creative, and compassionate. While few INFJ men ever achieve perfect relationships, they always wish for them. This is a positive quality when they stay in a committed relationship but it works against them when they move from one woman to another, always seeking a partner who lives up to their ideals.
If you’re in a relationship with an INFJ male, your feelings won’t go unnoticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Women as Lovers</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-women-as-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infj-women-as-lovers/</guid>
      <description>The INFJ female is an intense, passionate woman. She is drawn to the opposite sex, but few of them turn out to be long-term partners because they’re the wrong type. Still, the woman keeps trying. If she finally meets a man with a compatible personality and finds him moderately attractive, the connection usually strengthens.
The INFJ woman is compassionate, intelligent, and creative. While she longs for a perfect relationship, she seldom achieves her goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJs smile</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infjs-smile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/infjs-smile/</guid>
      <description>In days when it seems hard to be an INFJ, it’s worth looking at some of the qualities that come with this Myers-Briggs personality type. We may be only 1 percent of the population, but we have a lot of work to do in the world.
Actively contribute to the welfare of others.
Are patient and gentle with others but often hard on ourselves.
Lead others quietly; not imposing our will but influencing them behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Hard To Be an INFJ: The Author’s Personal Story</title>
      <link>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj-the-authors-personal-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BeaconStreetUSA.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj-the-authors-personal-story/</guid>
      <description>Since posting “It’s Hard To Be an INFJ” on this blog, I’ve received hundreds of e-mails from other INFJs. Their main theme has been how disconnected they’ve felt surrounded by extraverts and more sensible, earthbound types. Their posts and my responses appear after that blog.
This is my personal account of what it feels like to be an INFJ.
Growing up
As a child, I felt like an outsider. I’ve felt this way most of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
